

adam.drag@yahoo.com

206 619 0677

Phoenix, AZ

in linkedin.com/in/adamdrag

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3

Bootstrap, Sass

JavaScript, jQuery

WordPress, PHP

Node.js, Express.js

React

MySQL

MongoDB, Firebase

SEC

LAMP

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

LANGUAGES

English

00000

Polish

00000

Spanish

00

ADAM DRAG

Tech-savvy, self-starter with expertise and academic training in writing well-designed, testable and efficient code. Experienced in an array of scripting languages and multimedia Web tools. Able to handle dynamic workloads and optimize projects to exceed business goals. Proven team leader and team player with a positive, can-do attitude. Driven to continuously learn and improve.

WORK EXPERIENCE – United States

IntraEdge Phoenix, AZ

Feb 2019 to Present

Entry-Level Programmer

Attending Dev Training Program. Learning advanced programming, coding techniques and testing with exercises and group projects.

Cruise - General Motors Phoenix, AZ

Sept 2016 to Jan 2019

Intranet Developer

Designed, developed and maintained a custom company Intranet site for secure intradepartment communications, new policy acknowledgement, training tracking, Wiki, shift scheduling, project status and reporting in WordPress.

Team Lead

Led and trained Automated Vehicle Trainers team of 24 in testing automated vehicles. Managed garage operations, vehicle fleets and investigated/resolved AV system errors. Developed team management processes, in-vehicle training materials and procedures, and optimized AVT performance and communications.

Drive Classification Technician

Investigate and determine outcomes of automated vehicle system disengagments. Provide detailed analysis and classification for engineering resolution.

FALCK Northwest Seattle, WA

Sep 2015 – Aug 2016

Emergency Medical Technician

Provided ambulance and emergency services to public, including hospitals, clinics and extended-care facilities. Provided emergency services and patient support with perfect service call and ambulance driving record - 100% successful call completion.

PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE – International

Australia, England, Poland 2000 - 2015

Sales Manager: Managed daily operations in book wholesale. Developed and implemented operating procedures, managed budget, supervised staff, resolved client issues and ensured profitability.

Shop Manager: Managed daily operations of coffee shop. Maintained inventory, recruited and supervised staff including shift scheduling, supplier liaisons, managed budget, enforced hygiene and safety regulations and resolved customers issues.

EDUCATION

Full-stack developer, Coding Boot Camp, University of Arizona - 2019
Certificate of Information Technology, Kent Institute of Business and Technology – 2004
Business Diploma, Marketing, Australian Pacific College – 2007
Bachelor's Degree, Behavioral Psychology, Warsaw School of Pedagogy – 2002
Emergency Medical Technician, North Seattle College – 2015

SOFT SKILLS

Team leadership, operations management, process improvement, decision-making, teamwork, problem resolution, analysis and reporting.